walkscore.com 2012-05-01

# Walk Score - Helping homebuyers, renters, and real estate agents find houses and apartments in great neighborhoods.

By using Walk Score, a Front Seat Management, LLC ("FSM") website, you permit the collection and use of your personal information as outlined below in our Privacy Policy. You should visit this page periodically to review any changes to the Privacy Policy. 

## **1\. Information We Collect**

FSM collects user-submitted information such as street addresses. We collect email addresses if you join the Walk Score mailing list and we collect information from your Facebook profile when you use Facebook Connect. Some information collected is not explicitly submitted by the user. For example, we log your browser information, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp. 

## **2\. How We Use Your Information**

Information such as street addresses may be redisplayed on the Walk Score website or other FSM websites, for example in lists of the most or least walkable addresses. FSM will occasionally send email to the email addresses we collect for our mailing list

We use Facebook Connect to prevent abuse when people edit Walk Score information and to keep statistics about user edits. We may use information from your Facebook profile to contact you about Walk Score related features and we may redisplay your Facebook profile information and comments on the Walk Score website or other FSM websites. 

Browser-type related information, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp data help us diagnose problems with our server and administer Walk Score. In addition, we use this information to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the site and to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of users that have been exposed to, or clicked on, their advertising banners. 

## **3\. Transfer of Information**

FSM will disclose information about individual users to governmental or judicial authorities or law enforcement agencies, or to other individuals or entities in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal processes. Further, FSM may share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities or suspected fraud, or to enforce or apply the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. 

We reserve the right to transfer your personal information in the event of a transfer of ownership of Walk Score or FSM, such as an acquisition by or merger with another company. 

## **4\. Links**

Our website may contain links to third-party websites to which we have no affiliation. FSM does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. 

## **5\. Use of Cookies**

Like most websites, Walk Score may use cookies to refine our site and simplify our user experience. 

## **6\. Opting Out**

If you want FSM to cease sending you e-mail about the Services, you can discontinue such communication by following the instructions included in our e-mail.

## **7\. Children** ****

This website is not directed to children, and FSM does not knowingly solicit information from any child under the age of 13. 

## **8\. Terms and Modifications to this Privacy Statement**

By using the website, you signify your agreement to the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with these terms, you should not use the site. FSM may modify this Privacy Policy at any time. You are responsible for reviewing this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes to it. Your continued use of the site indicates your assent to any changes to this Privacy Policy. 

Walk Score uses the Google Maps API which has the following [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy.html). 

## **9\. Contacting Walk Score**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the privacy practices of this website, or if you want to exercise any of the rights that you are given under this Privacy Policy, you can contact us.

_Last modified 12/16/2010_
